<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://steviesnotes.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://steviesnotes.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2022-09-15T05:28:41+00:00</updated><id>https://steviesnotes.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>Steven Maloney&apos;s website... you get what you pay for. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">2020’s Christmas Letter</title><link href="https://steviesnotes.com/blog/2020/ChristmasCard/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2020’s Christmas Letter"/><published>2020-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://steviesnotes.com/blog/2020/ChristmasCard</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://steviesnotes.com/blog/2020/ChristmasCard/"><![CDATA[<div style="text-align: right"> December 2020<br/>Colorado Springs, CO </div> <p>Dear Family and Friends,</p> <p>I do apologize if this letter comes late in the holiday season, although I will blame that entirely on the slowing of the USPS and definitely not my procrastination in writing this letter. Ok, maybe I procrastinated a little bit.</p> <p>As with many others, time this year has seemed to go slower than ever and yet looking back at the year, it seems like Memorial Day only just happened. I began biking for exercise this year and to stay sane through the isolation. Originally training to complete the Denver Century Ride, I switched to training to bike up Pikes Peak once it became clear that the coronavirus would end all group activities this year. Pikes Peak is the eastern most 14,000+ foot mountain (14er) in the continental United States and one of six that I summited this year. A peak only 33 miles and 8000 feet vertically from my apartment, needless to say the descent was much more enjoyable than the ascent.</p> <p>Along with biking, I was able to enjoy a variety of hiking this year. Pictured on the card is one of my first hikes of the year, the famed Manitou Incline at sunrise. I was fortunate enough to hike with my family in Vermont while, as many others experienced this year, working remotely. I also explored many new trails out here in Colorado. I discovered the tree cover is a lot less than back in New England causing many sunburns early on. It took some time until I made it part of my routine before hiking, and to remember to reapply in the middle of some hikes.</p> <p>I am fortunate to have so much family here in Colorado. One highlight with family was my brother picking me up in a Cessna and flying me back to Denver for a fun weekend. A much more preferable way of getting to Denver than driving on the stretch of I-25 from Colorado Springs. I was also able to spend time with my cousins and their families. I was very happy to join them for gluten free pizza nights, which surprisingly tastes better than you think.</p> <p>Work this year has required a lot of patience at times as I have worked in a variety of roles and different programs. I am happy where I have landed though and am hoping to stay on this program for a while which makes this my first Christmas letter where I do not tell you about an upcoming move to another state.</p> <p>As the new year fast approaches, I need to remind myself that things will likely stay the same for much of the beginning of 2021 as we wait for the vaccine to be widely available. What I am hopeful for and will be working towards in 2021, is that the year ends better than it started.</p> <p>Best wishes,<br/> Steven</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christmas Letter written for Christmas 2020]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2019’s Christmas Letter</title><link href="https://steviesnotes.com/blog/2019/ChristmasCard/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2019’s Christmas Letter"/><published>2019-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://steviesnotes.com/blog/2019/ChristmasCard</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://steviesnotes.com/blog/2019/ChristmasCard/"><![CDATA[<div style="text-align: right"> December 2019<br/>Baltimore, MD</div> <p>Dear Family and Friends,</p> <p>I put off writing this letter for way too long, like many of my assignments for grad school (update one in my life: I started grad school at Georgia Tech). Hopefully next year I will be more on top of my life (don’t hold your breath).</p> <p>I can’t believe it has already been a year since my last card, I have moved between three states, graduated college, and started a full time job, or as one of my aunt’s would say, I have become a productive member of society. I spent most of 2019 in Baltimore, MD; A place too far south to be part of the Northeast and also too far north to be part of the South.</p> <p>Moving to a new city with no family or friends nearby made for a lonely start to the year, but that quickly changed when I started sailing. I was invited to deliver Artemis II for a race down the bay and for some reason was invited back aboard the following week to race, and then again and again. Sailing started out as a one night a week activity and in no time I found myself spending four or five nights a week on the water. I highly recommend that anyone coming to visit Baltimore set aside some time to enjoy Baltimore from the water.</p> <p>I moved down here this past February for work and have enjoyed the challenge that it has provided me. Moving into ASIC design was a natural transition from spending the previous summer in a semiconductor foundry. That being said, I am so grateful for the guidance from people in my department because there was still plenty I needed to learn. Just as I started this year moving to a new state for work, this coming year I am excited to be moving to Colorado Springs to start a new position within Northrop Grumman.</p> <p>The membership to the Downtown Sailing Center and the friends I met through it changed my view on the city. Baltimore went from a place I couldn’t wait to move onto the next place from to a place that I am sad to say goodbye to. As I look back at this past year I am reminded at what I said in last year’s christmas card and how this year has only reinforced it, friends are met in unique places at unexpected times. So, family and friends, new and old, please keep in touch, and please come out to visit me in Colorado Springs!</p> <p>I wish you happiness and health this holiday season and for the new year.</p> <p>Best,<br/> Steven</p> <p>P.S. I love seeing where my cards end up (last year they traveled a total of 47254 miles) so please if you have a chance to snap a selfie or take a picture of wherever you put Christmas cards send it my way.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christmas Letter written for Christmas 2019]]></summary></entry></feed>